{
    "id": "1eeea3ef85bb4ca1b41499faadc05be0",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I took him …………………… his brother. They are quite alike.",
            "description": "To take for is to mistake for another person.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0157cdb554404fec910d391801ebf0f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ……………………… with the best intentions.",
            "description": "To set out is to start a journey.",
            "answers": [
                "set in",
                "set down",
                "set out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "54ae94e03df044849c8713a5ed88b9c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The new chairman will …………………………… on 20th January.",
            "description": "To take over is to assume responsibility.",
            "answers": [
                "take out",
                "take in",
                "take over"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "89007c1c47714acf85c4539f3811f1da"
        },
        {
            "question": "When water was poured on his face, he soon came ………………………",
            "description": "To come around is to regain consciousness. ",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "around",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0a2e96070df046068b8a8648a38c7531"
        },
        {
            "question": "An orator must be good at getting his message …………………………….",
            "description": "To get your message across is to convey it. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "across",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5e06789e72fe419583e33981d1cd3feb"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is getting ……………………… well in his career.",
            "description": "To get on is to progress.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "along"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8a464721ae9347d38ad184b90262029b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He kept ………………………… asking silly questions.",
            "description": "To keep on is to continue.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "out",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "20454df638454c78b155a3931a9c865c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The government failed to …………………………… the riots.",
            "description": "To put down is to crush.",
            "answers": [
                "put put",
                "put down",
                "put off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5712ece435b44c548e73cc6793065002"
        },
        {
            "question": "They all look ……………………………… him as their leader.",
            "description": "To look up to somebody is to treat them with respect.",
            "answers": [
                "up to",
                "up",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c995c58b7242441a80d15393fa311848"
        },
        {
            "question": "Once he became successful, he began to look …………………………… his old friends.",
            "description": "To look down on somebody is to treat them with contempt.",
            "answers": [
                "down",
                "below",
                "down on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c21afe0249894022847f0451289204d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor advised him to abstain …………………………… alcoholic drinks.",
            "description": "To abstain from is to refrain him.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "from",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7120681706ad4a47985622dcd072b1c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He had promised to lend me some money, but he backed ………………………… later.",
            "description": "To back out is to withdraw from a promise. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e3e69d62d5bd4c7080b38fb5dffd8408"
        }
    ]
}